CHOKRI BEN CHOKRI

Full Stack Developer

- **** +216 95636012
- https://chokriben.github.io
- Sfax

- @ chokribenmahjoub@gmail.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/chokri-ben-mahjoub



SUMMARY

Versatile and autonomous, Full Stack Developer with a passion for programming, development, analysis, and data visualization. Motivated to drive projects forward and seek innovative solutions. Consistently rewarded for success in planning and operational improvements. Experienced in policy development and staff management procedures, positively impacting overall morale and productivity.

EXPERIENCE

01/2024 - Present •

Sfax, Tunisia

Full Stack Developer

APBS Groupe - Intégrateur de Solutions de Gestion Sage

- Tracked customer shipment requirements to improve customer satisfaction while increasing service efficiencies in Sfax, Tunisia
- · Design and implement interactive and user-friendly user interfaces using Vue.js.
- \cdot $\,$ Quickly identify and resolve problems encountered during development or in production.
- · Technical environment: Vue JS, Github, Devexpress, Entity framework, Dapper, SQL server

12/2022 - 12/2023 •

Full Stack Developer

Sfax, Tunisia

Infotech Consulting Services ICS

- · Participate in the creation of new APIs, including testing using of postman to check their operation (backend side)
- · Develop new services on the backend side to support load the necessary features
- · Create new interfaces and pages on the frontend side to provide improved user experience
- · Technical environment: vuetify, Laravel, API Postman, Nuxt.js, Vue.js 3, docker, JIRA, MySQL

11/2021 - 10/2022

Sfax, Tunisia

Software Developer

Logicom

- · Receive, record and follow up on customer complaints in Sfax, Tunisia
- Design, develop and maintain ERP modules specific, including those linked to commercial management, stock management, and management of crate production sites
- · Technical environment: Visual Basic .NET (VB.NET), C sharp, Svn, and Mysgl

02/2020 - 07/2020

Intern (end Of Study Internship)

Sfax, Tunisia

Leader tec Engineering

- · Intern (end Of Study Internship) at Leader Tec Engineering in Sfax, Tunisia
- · Allow the recording of supplier information, including their contact details, the products they supply, prices agreed
- · Associate orders with corresponding customers and products
- · Technical environment: Php, android studio et mysgl

SKILLS

Donet	DevExpress	Docker	Flutter	Java	Laravel	MySQL	Php	React js	SQL Server
VB.Net	Vue js								

EDUCATION

12/2022 - 11/2024 •

Sfax, Tunisia

- Development Of Computer Systems And Networks

 Higher Institute of Technological Studies of Sfax ISET
- · Software engineering and new technology

10/2017 - 07/2020

Sfax, Tunisia

- Basic License In Computer Science
 The Higher Institute Of Computer Science And Multimedia
 - · Web and multimedia development